Guide to the Knights dOrleans records
Louisiana Research Collection
Knights dOrleans records 1993-2006
LaRC/Manuscripts Collection 986
Knights dOrleans (Organization)
5.00
2.5 linear feet
Louisiana Research Collection 202 Jones Hall 6801 Freret Street New Orleans, LA, URL: http://specialcollections.tulane.edu/archon Email: sbenjam@tulane.edu Phone: 504-865-5685
Biographical Information:
The Knights dOrleans was founded in 1974. According to the organizations bylaws, the purpose of this organization shall be the binding together of persons with shared interests in leather and levi and to promote brotherhood, service and aid to the community. The New Orleans-based club assists various Carnival krewes with staffing, presenting, and providing security for events. It also raises funds for its annual Anniversary Run and for other club, social, civic, and charitable activities.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Knights dOrleans (Organization)
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records.; Application forms.; Brochures.; Correspondence.; Financial records.; Membership lists.; Minutes.; Photographs.; Stationery.
Geographic Name:
New Orleans (La.) -- Social life and customs -- 20th century.; New Orleans (La.) -- Social life and customs -- 21st century.
Topical Term:
Carnival -- Louisiana -- New Orleans.; Gay clubs -- Louisiana -- New Orleans.; Gay community -- Louisiana -- New Orleans.; Gays -- Louisiana -- New Orleans.; Leather clubs (Organizations)
Administrative Information
Acquisition Information:
Gift.
Accruals:
Additions to the collection may occur in the future.
Conditions Governing Access:
Collection is open to the public. No known restrictions.
Arrangement of Materials:
Arranged generally in chronological order, to accommodate accretions. The collection consists of 5 boxes. It is 2.5 linear feet.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes the clubs constitution and bylaws, minutes, brochures, stationery, membership rosters, financial records, property inventory, photographs, correspondence, and memorabilia of activities. The club assists various Carnival krewes with staffing, presenting, and providing security for events. It also raises funds for its annual Anniversary Run and for other club, social, civic, and charitable activities.
Detailed List of Contents
- Constitution, bylaws, membership, and early history, id118154 (Box 1)
  - Constitution and bylaws, 1996 and undated; id127785 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Brochures, stationery, and stickers, undated; id127786 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dues, 2000-2002; id127787 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Membership roster, 1999 and undated; id127788 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Club property inventory, 1997-2004; id127789 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, undated; id127790 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Membership forms/applications, 1980-2001; id127791 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Incomplete set of run pins, 1999 and undated; id127792 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Club records and papers, prior 1993; id127793 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 20th anniversary run, and records, 1993-2004; 1997-2000; id118155 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1993; id127794 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1999; id127795 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 2000; id127796 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 2001; id127797 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 2002; id127798 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 2003; id127799 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 2004; id127800 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Twentieth Anniversary Run, 1994 September/October; id127801 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Records, 1997 February; id127802 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Records, 1997 March; id127803 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Records, 1997 May; id127804 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Records, 1997 August; id127805 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Records, 1997 September; id127806 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Records, 1997 October; id127807 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Records, 1998 October; id127808 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Records, 1998 December; id127809 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Records, 1999 January; id127810 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Records, 1999 February; id127811 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Records, 1999 May; id127812 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Records, 1999 June; id127813 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Records, 1999 July; id127814 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Records, 1999 August; id127815 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Records, 1999 September; id127816 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Records, 1999 October; id127817 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Records, 1999 November; id127818 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Records, 1999 December; id127819 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Records, 2000 January; id127820 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Records, 2000 February; id127821 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Records, 2000 March; id127822 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Records, 2000 April; id127823 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Records, 2000 May; id127824 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Records, 2000 June; id127825 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Records, 2000 July; id127826 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Records, 2000 August; id127827 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Records, 2000 September; id127828 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Records, 2000 October; id127829 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Records, 2000 November; id127830 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Records, 2000 December; id127831 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Records and Mr. and Mrs. Knight contest, 2001-2004; id118156 (Box 3)
  - Records, 2001 January; id127832 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Records, 2001 February; id127833 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Records, 2001 March; id127834 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Records, 2001 April; id127835 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Records, 2001 May; id127836 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Records, 2001 June; id127837 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Records, 2001 July; id127838 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Records, 2001 August; id127839 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Records, 2001 September; id127840 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Records, 2001 October; id127841 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Records, 2001 November; id127842 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Records, 2001 December; id127843 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Records, 2002 January; id127844 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Records, 2002 February; id127845 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Records, 2002 March; id127846 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Records, 2002 April; id127847 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Records, 2002 May; id127848 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Knight Contest, 2002 May 17; id127849 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Records, 2002 June; id127850 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Records, 2002 July; id127851 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Records, 2002 August; id127852 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Records, 2002 September; id127853 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Records, 2002 October; id127854 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Records, 2002 November; id127855 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Records, 2002 December; id127856 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Records, 2003 January; id127857 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Records, 2003 February; id127858 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Records, 2003 March; id127859 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Records, 2003 April; id127860 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Records, 2003 May; id127861 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Records, 2003 June; id127862 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Records, 2003 July; id127863 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Records, 2003 August; id127864 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Records, 2003 September; id127865 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Records, 2003 October; id127866 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Records, 2003 November; id127867 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Records, 2003 December; id127868 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Records, 2004 January; id127869 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Records, 2004 February; id127870 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Records, 2004 March; id127871 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Records, 2004 April; id127872 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Records, 2004 May; id127873 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Records, 2004 June; id127874 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Records, 2004 July; id127875 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Records, 2004 August; id127876 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Records, 2004 September; id127877 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Records, 2004 October; id127878 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Records, 2005-2006; id118157 (Box 4)
  - Records, 2005; id127879 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Records, 2006; id127880 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Unprocessed additions, id118158 (Box 5)